TASK:
Select Janella from the list and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: dropdown, X: 76 [0-151], Y: 66 [56-76], text: "Storm"}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a click_element action, to interact with the dropdown menu on the screen. The dropdown menu, identified as demo_element_1, was located at the center of the screen with coordinates X: 76 [0-151] and Y: 66 [56-76], and had the text "Storm" visible on it. Clicking on this dropdown was necessary to expand the list of options and select the desired item, "Janella," from the list. The dropdown needed to be expanded because the task required selecting a specific item that was not currently visible or selectable on the screen. After the action was performed, the dropdown menu remained visible, but the "Submit" button (demo_element_2) became temporarily invisible, indicating that the dropdown list expanded over it. New elements appeared on the screen, which were the options within the dropdown menu, including "Selie," "Janella," "Storm" (now highlighted to indicate it was the previously selected option), "Gena," "Betti," and "Chrissie," with their respective coordinates and visibility status. This expansion allowed the expert to proceed with selecting "Janella" from the list."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 76 [0-151], Y: 117 [109-125], text: "Janella"}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a click_element action, to select "Janella" from the dropdown list. This action was necessary because the task required selecting a specific name, "Janella," from the list of options that appeared after expanding the dropdown menu. The expert identified the correct element to click by its type (tabled_text), its coordinates (X: 76 [0-151], Y: 117 [109-125]), and its text content ("Janella"), which was visible on the screen among other options. After clicking on "Janella," the dropdown list collapsed, making the "Submit" button (demo_element_2) visible again, and the dropdown menu now displayed "Janella" as the selected item. The other names in the list ("Selie," "Storm," "Gena," "Betti," and "Chrissie") were no longer visible, indicating that the dropdown had retracted and the task could proceed to the next step, which was to click the "Submit" button."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 96 [79-112], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a click_element action, to interact with the "Submit" button on the screen. This action was necessary to complete the task of selecting "Janella" from the dropdown list and then submitting the choice. The "Submit" button was identified by its type (button), its coordinates (X: 50 [1-98], Y: 96 [79-112]), and its text content ("Submit"), which was visible and accessible on the screen. Clicking the "Submit" button was the final step required to confirm the selection of "Janella" and proceed with the task. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application or window that was previously open had closed or moved to the next stage, leaving no elements visible on the screen."}

