TASK:
Select UusOQFG, 0Z and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 42 [8-76], Y: 62 [54-69], text: "UusOQFG"}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to select the checkbox associated with the text "UusOQFG." This action was necessary because the task required selecting specific items, in this case, "UusOQFG," before clicking the "Submit" button. The checkbox for "UusOQFG" was identified by its screen coordinates: the center of the checkbox was at X: 42 and Y: 62, with the left and right edges spanning from X: 8 to X: 76, and the top and bottom edges from Y: 54 to Y: 69. After the action was performed, the status of the checkbox changed to 'checked: True,' indicating that the checkbox was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by a visual indication (such as a checkmark) within the checkbox, signifying that "UusOQFG" was chosen as part of the task requirements."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 24 [9-40], Y: 100 [92-107], text: "0Z"}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `click_element` action, to select the checkbox associated with the text "0Z." This action was necessary because the task required selecting specific items, and "0Z" was one of them. The checkbox for "0Z" was identified by its screen coordinates: the center of the checkbox was at X: 24 and Y: 100, with the left and right edges spanning from X: 9 to X: 40, and the top and bottom edges from Y: 92 to Y: 107. After the action was performed, the status of the checkbox changed to 'checked: True,' indicating that the checkbox was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by a visual indication (such as a checkmark) within the checkbox, signifying that "0Z" was chosen as part of the task requirements. The expert's choice of action was based on the task's instruction to select "0Z," and the action was executed by clicking on the checkbox corresponding to that item."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [2-98], Y: 173 [157-189], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to click on the "Submit" button after selecting the required checkboxes. This action was necessary to complete the task of submitting the selected options. The "Submit" button was identified by its screen coordinates: the center of the button was at X: 50 and Y: 173, with the left and right edges spanning from X: 2 to X: 98, and the top and bottom edges from Y: 157 to Y: 189. The button was labeled with the text "Submit" and was visible on the screen. Clicking this button was the final step in the task, as it would process the selections made by the user. After the action was performed, the task was completed successfully, resulting in an empty screen, which indicates that the previous interface with the checkboxes and the "Submit" button was no longer displayed, and the user's selections were submitted as intended."}

