TASK:
Select Naoma, Silva from the scroll list and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 68 [2-133], Y: 66 [57-74], text: "Silva"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a left-click on the screen element with the text "Silva," to select this item from the scroll list. The action was necessary because "Silva" was one of the names that needed to be selected for the task. The expert chose to click on the element with coordinates X: 68 [2-133], Y: 66 [57-74], which refers to the horizontal center (X: 68) and vertical center (Y: 66) of the element's location on the screen, with the left and right edges of the element at X: 2 and X: 133, respectively, and the top and bottom edges at Y: 57 and Y: 74. After the action was performed, the status of the screen showed that the "Silva" element was highlighted, indicating that it was successfully selected. The highlighted state is a visual confirmation that the item is now marked for any subsequent actions, such as being included in a group selection or being the target of a command like "Submit.""}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: scrollbar_down_button, X: 142 [134-151], Y: 138 [130-147]}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which was a left-click on the down button of the scrollbar/spinner (demo_element_8), located at the coordinates X: 142 [134-151], Y: 138 [130-147]. This action was necessary to scroll down the list and bring additional items into view. The down button is typically located on the right side of a scrollable list, and clicking it moves the list content upwards, revealing items that were previously off-screen at the bottom. After the action was taken, the screen status changed: the previously visible items "Silva," "Lexi," and "Lia" were no longer visible, indicating they had been scrolled out of view. The scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_4) also moved down, from Y: 87 [75-99] to Y: 98 [86-110], reflecting the scrolling action. New items, "Naoma" and "Bebe," appeared on the screen (demo_element_10 and demo_element_11, respectively), with "Naoma" being one of the names required for the task. This change in the screen elements' visibility confirms that the list was successfully scrolled to display additional names."}
action_4: {name: control_click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 68 [2-133], Y: 111 [103-119], text: "Naoma"}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which was a control-click on the screen element with the text "Naoma," to select this item in addition to the already selected "Silva" without deselecting it. This action was necessary because the task required selecting both "Naoma" and "Silva" from the scroll list. The control-click is a standard method for selecting multiple items in a list. The expert chose to click on the element with coordinates X: 68 [2-133], Y: 111 [103-119], which refers to the horizontal center (X: 68) and vertical center (Y: 111) of the element's location on the screen. After the action was performed, the status of the screen showed that both "Silva" and "Naoma" were highlighted, indicating that they were successfully selected together. The highlighted state is a visual confirmation that both items are now marked for any subsequent actions, such as being included in a group selection or being the target of a command like "Submit.""}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [2-97], Y: 168 [152-183], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_5 was a left-click on the "Submit" button, which is a standard user interface element for confirming or finalizing an action. The expert chose this action because the task was to select two specific names, "Naoma" and "Silva," from a scroll list and then click "Submit" to complete the task. The "Submit" button was identified as demo_element_9 with its center coordinates at X: 50 [2-97], Y: 168 [152-183], indicating its horizontal center (X: 50) and vertical center (Y: 168) within the screen's coordinate system. The button was visible and located within the boundaries defined by the left and right edges (X: 2 and X: 97, respectively) and the top and bottom edges (Y: 152 and Y: 183, respectively). The action was necessary to confirm the selection of the two names and proceed with the task. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the interface for the task was no longer displayed, which is a common response after submitting a form or completing a task in a software application."}

