TASK:
Switch between the tabs to find and click on the link "orci".

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: hyperlink, X: 50 [42-58], Y: 154 [148-159], text: "orci"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, with the argument specifying the element_id corresponding to the hyperlink with the text "orci". This action was chosen because the task was to find and click on the link "orci". On the screen, there were several elements including text and hyperlinks, but the expert identified demo_element_13 as the target because it matched the text "orci". This element was a hyperlink, located at the center coordinates X: 50 [42-58], Y: 154 [148-159], and was visible on the screen. By clicking on this hyperlink, the expert completed the task as required. After the action was performed, the screen status was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and likely triggered a navigation event or action that led to a different screen or state, which is why the screen was empty."}

