TASK:
Select uAACh, bfJYlLi, 4fY, OoM, usOQF, yeIAM, 6ViJ, NsDATJ, O0mVgSt, Ts and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 34 [8-61], Y: 138 [131-145], text: "uAACh"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a `click_element` action, to select the checkbox corresponding to the text "uAACh". This action was necessary because the task required selecting specific items, including "uAACh", by clicking their associated checkboxes. The checkbox for "uAACh" was identified on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 34 and Y: 138, within the horizontal range of 8 to 61 and the vertical range of 131 to 145, indicating its position on the screen. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that the checkbox was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, visually confirming that "uAACh" was part of the selection set for the task."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 92 [67-118], Y: 100 [92-108], text: "bfJYlLi"}, reason: "The expert chose action_3, which was a `click_element` action, to select the checkbox associated with the text "bfJYlLi". This action was necessary because the task required selecting specific items listed on the screen, and "bfJYlLi" was one of them. The checkbox for "bfJYlLi" was identified on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 92 and Y: 100, within the horizontal range of 67 to 118 and the vertical range of 92 to 108. The expert needed to click this checkbox to include "bfJYlLi" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "bfJYlLi" was part of the selection set."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 26 [9-44], Y: 156 [149-164], text: "4fy"}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which was a `click_element` action, with the argument specifying the checkbox associated with the text "4fy". This action was necessary because "4fy" was one of the items listed in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "4fy" was identified on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 26 and Y: 156, within the horizontal range of 9 to 44 and the vertical range of 149 to 164. By clicking this checkbox, the expert included "4fy" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "4fy" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 88 [67-109], Y: 138 [131-146], text: "OoM"}, reason: "The expert performed action_5, which was a `click_element` action, with the argument specifying the checkbox associated with the text "OoM". This action was chosen because "OoM" was one of the items listed in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "OoM" was identified on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 88 and Y: 138, within the horizontal range of 67 to 109 and the vertical range of 131 to 146. By clicking this checkbox, the expert included "OoM" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "OoM" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 34 [9-60], Y: 62 [54-70], text: "usOQF"}, reason: "Action_6 was a `click_element` action targeting the checkbox associated with the text "usOQF." The expert chose this action because "usOQF" was one of the items specified in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "usOQF" was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 34 and Y: 62, within the horizontal range of 9 to 60 and the vertical range of 54 to 70. This action was necessary to include "usOQF" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "usOQF" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_7: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 32 [8-57], Y: 81 [73-89], text: "yeIAM"}, reason: "The expert performed action_7, which was a `click_element` action, with the argument specifying the checkbox associated with the text "yeIAM". This action was chosen because "yeIAM" was one of the items listed in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "yeIAM" was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 32 and Y: 81, within the horizontal range of 8 to 57 and the vertical range of 73 to 89. Clicking this checkbox was necessary to include "yeIAM" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "yeIAM" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_8: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 88 [68-107], Y: 62 [54-70], text: "6ViJ"}, reason: "The expert performed action_8, which was a `click_element` action, with the argument specifying the checkbox associated with the text "6ViJ". This action was chosen because "6ViJ" was one of the items listed in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "6ViJ" was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 88 and Y: 62, within the horizontal range of 68 to 107 and the vertical range of 54 to 70. Clicking this checkbox was necessary to include "6ViJ" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "6ViJ" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_9: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 96 [67-124], Y: 81 [73-89], text: "NsDATJ"}, reason: "Action_9 was a `click_element` action targeting the checkbox associated with the text "NsDATJ." The expert chose this action because "NsDATJ" was one of the items specified in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "NsDATJ" was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 96 and Y: 81, within the horizontal range of 67 to 124 and the vertical range of 73 to 89. This action was necessary to include "NsDATJ" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "NsDATJ" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_10: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 99 [67-131], Y: 119 [111-127], text: "O0mVgSt"}, reason: "The expert performed action_10, which was a `click_element` action, with the argument specifying the checkbox associated with the text "O0mVgSt". This action was chosen because "O0mVgSt" was one of the items listed in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "O0mVgSt" was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 99 and Y: 119, within the horizontal range of 67 to 131 and the vertical range of 111 to 127. Clicking this checkbox was necessary to include "O0mVgSt" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "O0mVgSt" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_11: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 24 [9-38], Y: 119 [111-127], text: "Ts"}, reason: "Action_11 was a `click_element` action targeting the checkbox associated with the text "Ts". The expert chose this action because "Ts" was one of the items listed in the task that needed to be selected. The checkbox for "Ts" was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 24 and Y: 119, within the horizontal range of 9 to 38 and the vertical range of 111 to 127. This action was necessary to include "Ts" in the selection set for the task. After the action was executed, the status of the checkbox changed to `checked: True`, indicating that it was successfully selected. This change was reflected on the screen by the checkbox now being marked or highlighted, confirming that "Ts" was part of the selection set. The visibility of the checkbox remained true, meaning it was still visible on the screen after the action."}
action_12: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [2-98], Y: 182 [166-197], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_12, which was a `click_element` action, with the argument specifying the button with the text "Submit". This action was chosen because, after selecting all the required checkboxes corresponding to the items listed in the task (uAACh, bfJYlLi, 4fy, OoM, usOQF, yeIAM, 6ViJ, NsDATJ, O0mVgSt, Ts), the next step was to submit the selections. The "Submit" button was located on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 50 and Y: 182, within the horizontal range of 2 to 98 and the vertical range of 166 to 197. Clicking this button was necessary to complete the task and submit the selected items. After the action was executed, the screen status changed to an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the previous interface with checkboxes and the submit button was no longer displayed. This typically means that the system has accepted the selections and is processing the request or has navigated to a different page or state as a result of the submission."}

