TASK:
Switch between the tabs to find and click on the link "nec".

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: hyperlink, X: 74 [66-82], Y: 122 [117-126], text: "nec"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, with the argument specifying the hyperlink type and coordinates X: 74 [66-82], Y: 122 [117-126], with the text "nec". This action was chosen because the task was to find and click on the link "nec". The expert identified demo_element_6 as the target because it matched the description: it was a hyperlink (clickable text that leads to another page or action), located at the center coordinates X: 74, Y: 122, within the horizontal range of 66 to 82 and the vertical range of 117 to 126, and it had the visible text "nec". Clicking on this hyperlink was necessary to complete the task as it was the specified goal. After the action was performed, the screen status was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully, which typically means that the click on the hyperlink "nec" led to a navigation event, taking the user away from the current screen to the destination linked by "nec"."}

