TASK:
Select nothing and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [2-98], Y: 135 [119-151], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a `click_element` action, to complete the task of submitting without selecting any checkboxes. The argument for this action specified the coordinates and the text of the "Submit" button, which was located at the center of the screen with coordinates X: 50 [2-98], Y: 135 [119-151]. This button was visible and needed to be activated to submit the form. The expert chose to click this button directly because the task was to "Select nothing and click Submit," which implies that none of the checkboxes (demo_element_1, demo_element_2, demo_element_3) needed to be interacted with. After the action was performed, the screen was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the form was likely submitted, resulting in the user being taken to a different screen or the application closing."}

