TASK:
Click on a "text" widget.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 114 [103-126], text: "MT"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, with the argument specifying the input_field type element with coordinates X: 66 [1-130], Y: 114 [103-126], containing the text "MT". This action was chosen because the task was to click on a "text" widget, and among the visible elements on the screen, demo_element_5 was an input_field that contained text, which is a type of text widget. The expert likely interpreted the task as requiring interaction with an element where text can be entered or edited, rather than a static text display like demo_element_2, demo_element_4, or demo_element_8. The input_field at demo_element_5 was visible and had the coordinates and text content that matched the action's argument. After the action was completed, the screen was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and that clicking the input_field with the text "MT" was the correct action to fulfill the task requirements."}

