TASK:
Click on a "text" widget.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 90 [78-101], text: "MwmJ"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, with the argument specifying the input_field type element with coordinates X: 66 [1-130], Y: 90 [78-101], and containing the text "MwmJ". This action was chosen because the task was to click on a "text" widget, and among the visible elements on the screen, demo_element_3 was the only one that matched the description of being an input field that could contain text. The coordinates and text content of demo_element_3 confirm that it was the target for the click. The action was necessary to interact with the specified widget as per the task's instructions. After the action was completed, the screen status was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully, and the click on the input field likely triggered a transition or completed the task, resulting in an empty screen."}

