TASK:
Click on a "text" widget.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 66 [55-78], text: "3S"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, with the argument specifying the coordinates and the type of the element to interact with. The expert chose to click on the input field with the text "3S" because the task was to click on a "text" widget. Among the elements listed, demo_element_3 and demo_element_8 are of type "text," but the coordinates given in action_2 match those of demo_element_1, which is an input field containing the text "3S" (centered at X: 66, Y: 66, within the horizontal range of 1-130 and the vertical range of 55-78). The expert's action was necessary to fulfill the task's requirement to interact with a text widget, which in this case was interpreted as clicking on the input field that contains text. After the action was completed, the screen was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and that the click on the input field was the correct action to achieve the desired outcome."}

