TASK:
Click on a "text" widget.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 67 [56-78], text: "ehH"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, to complete the task of clicking on a "text" widget. The arguments for this action included the coordinates and the type of the element to interact with. The expert chose to click on demo_element_1, which is described as an input field with its center located at X: 66 and Y: 67, within the horizontal range of 1 to 130 and the vertical range of 56 to 78, containing the text "ehH". This element was visible on the screen, making it the target for the task. The reason for this action was to activate or focus on the text widget, which in this case was an input field where text can be entered. After the action was completed, the screen was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and that there was no further interaction required with the screen elements."}

