TASK:
Copy the text from the 3rd text area below and paste it into the text input, then press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: text, X: 22 [4-39], Y: 127 [122-132], text: "Poten"}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the third text area where the text to be copied is located. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the element to interact with. The expert clicked on the text "Poten," which is part of the text within the third text area (demo_element_15), located at the center coordinates X: 22 [4-39], Y: 127 [122-132]. This action was necessary to set the focus on the third text area so that subsequent actions could be performed on the text within it, such as selecting all (Ctrl+A) and copying (Ctrl+C). After the action was performed, the status of the computer screen showed that the third text area (demo_element_13) became focused, as indicated by the attribute `focused: True`. Additionally, the text "tit" from demo_element_18 became invisible, and a new text "ri" appeared in demo_element_21, suggesting that the content of the text area might have been scrolled or updated as a result of the click, revealing additional text that was not previously visible."}
action_3: {name: press_control_A, arg: {}, reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `press_control_A` action, to select all the text within the focused text area (demo_element_13). This action was necessary because the task required copying the text from the third text area, and using the 'Select All' command is a quick way to highlight all the text in a text area without having to manually click and drag the mouse to select it. The third text area was already focused from the previous action (action_2), which means that any subsequent text operation would apply to this area. After action_3 was performed, the status of the computer screen showed that the text "ri" in demo_element_21 and the text "Potren" in demo_element_22 were highlighted, indicating that the 'Select All' command successfully selected the text in the focused text area, making it ready to be copied with the next action. The visibility of the text "Poten" changed from visible to false and then to true with highlighting, which suggests that the text was part of the selection and the screen updated to reflect the selection state."}
action_4: {name: press_control_C, arg: {}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `press_control_C` action, to copy the selected text from the focused text area (demo_element_13) to the clipboard. This action was necessary because the task required copying the text "Potrenri" (as indicated by the highlighted text in demo_element_21 and demo_element_22) from the third text area to be pasted elsewhere. The `press_control_C` action does not require any arguments as it is a keyboard shortcut that operates on the currently selected text, which was highlighted by the previous `press_control_A` action. After action_4 was performed, there was no visible change on the screen because the action of copying text to the clipboard does not alter the visual state of the screen components. The text remained highlighted in demo_element_21 and demo_element_22, indicating that it was still selected and ready for the next operation, which would be pasting the text into the input field (demo_element_19)."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 164 [153-175], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_5, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the copied text needed to be pasted. The arguments for this action specify the type of element (input_field), and the coordinates (X: 66 [1-130], Y: 164 [153-175]) where the input field is located on the screen. This action was necessary to set the focus on the input field (demo_element_19), which was empty and visible, so that the subsequent paste action (Ctrl+V) could insert the copied text into this field. After action_5 was performed, the status of the computer screen showed that the input field (demo_element_19) became focused, as indicated by the attribute `focused: True`. The text within the third text area (demo_element_13) that was previously highlighted ("Potrenri" from demo_element_21 and demo_element_22) was no longer visible, indicating that the focus had shifted away from the text area to the input field."}
action_6: {name: press_control_V, arg: {}, reason: "The expert performed action_6, which is a `press_control_V` action, to paste the previously copied text into the focused input field. This action was necessary because the task required transferring the text from the third text area to the input field. The `press_control_V` action is a keyboard shortcut for pasting and does not require any arguments since it operates on the system clipboard and the currently focused element, which in this case was the input field (demo_element_19). The input field was already focused from the previous action (action_5), ensuring that the pasted content would go into the correct location. After action_6 was executed, the text "s adipiscing tempus " appeared in the input field (demo_element_19), indicating that the paste operation was successful. The input field remained focused, and the text was visible, confirming that the pasted content was now ready for submission, which aligns with the next step in the task."}
action_7: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 193 [178-208], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_7, which is a `click_element` action, to submit the text that was pasted into the input field. The arguments for this action specify the type of element (button), and the coordinates (X: 50 [1-98], Y: 193 [178-208]) where the "Submit" button is located on the screen. This action was necessary to complete the task of submitting the text that was copied from the third text area and pasted into the input field (demo_element_19). The "Submit" button (demo_element_20) was visible and needed to be activated to finalize the submission process. After the action was executed, the screen status showed an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully, and the application or form that was being interacted with had likely processed the submission and moved to a different state or screen, which is why no elements were displayed anymore."}

