TASK:
Sort the numbers in increasing order, starting with the lowest number at the top of the list.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [2-98], Y: 188 [173-204], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to interact with a button labeled "Submit" (demo_element_5). This button was located at the center coordinates X: 50, Y: 188, with its horizontal range from 2 to 98 and vertical range from 173 to 204. The reason for this action was to submit the current order of numbers for evaluation, as the task was to sort the numbers in increasing order. The expert must have previously arranged the draggable text elements (demo_element_1 to demo_element_4), which represented the numbers -26, -10, -4, and 17, in the correct increasing order before hitting the "Submit" button. After the action was performed, the screen was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully, and the correct order of numbers was submitted, as there were no further instructions or elements displayed on the screen."}

