TASK:
Enter the password "Ieh" into both text fields and press submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 60 [6-115], Y: 88 [77-99], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the first input field where the password needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the type of the element to interact with. In this case, the expert targeted demo_element_2, an input field located at the center coordinates X: 60 and Y: 88, with the left and right edges spanning from 6 to 115 and the top and bottom edges from 77 to 99, respectively. This input field was visible and initially unfocused, as indicated by the absence of the "focused" attribute. The action was necessary to place the cursor inside the input field so that text could be entered into it. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed to show that demo_element_2, the first input field, was now focused, as indicated by the addition of the "focused: True" attribute. This focus allowed for text entry into the field, which was the next step in completing the task of entering the password."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Ieh", reason: "Action_3 was a `type_text` action with the argument "Ieh," which was chosen by the expert to enter the password into the first input field that was already focused. The expert had previously clicked on demo_element_2, an input field for the password, to place the cursor inside it. This field is located at the center coordinates X: 60 and Y: 88, with its dimensions spanning from X: 6 to 115 and Y: 77 to 99. The field was empty and ready to receive input, as indicated by the text attribute being an empty string and the focused attribute being set to True. Typing the password was necessary to fulfill the task requirement of entering the password into both text fields. After the action was completed, the screen status showed that the text "•••" appeared in demo_element_2, indicating that the password was entered and masked for security purposes. The field remained focused, allowing for further interaction if needed."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 60 [6-115], Y: 140 [128-151], text: ""}, reason: "Action_4 was a `click_element` action chosen by the expert to focus on the second input field, where the password needed to be verified. The expert targeted demo_element_4, an input field labeled "Verify password," located at the center coordinates X: 60 and Y: 140, with the left and right edges spanning from 6 to 115 and the top and bottom edges from 128 to 151, respectively. This field was initially unfocused and empty, as indicated by the absence of the "focused" attribute and the text attribute being an empty string. Focusing on this field was necessary to enter the password again for verification purposes, as per the task requirement. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to show that demo_element_4 was now focused, as indicated by the addition of the "focused: True" attribute, and ready for the password to be entered into it."}
action_5: {name: type_text, arg: "Ieh", reason: "Action_5 was a `type_text` action with the argument "Ieh," chosen by the expert to enter the password into the second input field, which was already focused and ready for text entry. This field, demo_element_4, is an input field for verifying the password, located at the center coordinates X: 60 and Y: 140, with its dimensions spanning from X: 6 to 115 and Y: 128 to 151. It was necessary to type the password into this field to meet the task requirement of entering the password into both text fields for verification purposes. After the action was completed, the screen status showed that the text "•••" appeared in demo_element_4, indicating that the password was entered and masked for security purposes, and the field remained focused, signifying that the text was successfully inputted and the field was still active for further interaction if needed."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 56 [7-105], Y: 180 [164-197], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_6 was a `click_element` action chosen by the expert to activate the "Submit" button, which is necessary to complete the task of entering the password into both text fields and submitting the information. The "Submit" button, identified as demo_element_5, is a button-type element located at the center coordinates X: 56 and Y: 180, with its dimensions spanning from X: 7 to 105 and Y: 164 to 197. The text on the button reads "Submit," and it is visible on the screen. By clicking this button, the expert signaled the completion of the password entry process, instructing the system to accept and process the entered data. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the interface had transitioned away from the password entry screen, likely to a subsequent stage in the application or process."}

