TASK:
Enter "Hj" into the text field and press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 74 [10-139], Y: 72 [60-83], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to activate the input field so that text could be entered into it. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the type of the screen element to interact with. In this case, the input field was located at the center coordinates X: 74 and Y: 72, with the horizontal range from 10 to 139 and the vertical range from 60 to 83. This input field was initially empty and visible on the screen, as indicated by the text attribute being an empty string and the visible attribute being True. The action was necessary because, in order to type text into an input field, the field must first be focused, which is achieved by clicking on it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was now focused, as shown by the addition of the focused attribute set to True. This focus allowed for text entry in the subsequent steps of the task. The Submit button remained unchanged, still visible on the screen with its specified coordinates."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Hj", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `type_text` action, to enter the specified text "Hj" into the already focused input field. This action was necessary because the task required entering text into the text field, and since action_2 had already focused the input field (demo_element_1), it was ready for text entry. The input field was described as having its center at coordinates X: 74 and Y: 72, with a horizontal range from 10 to 139 and a vertical range from 60 to 83, indicating its position and size on the screen. It was also marked as focused and visible, which are the required states for text entry. After the `type_text` action was performed, the text "Hj" appeared within the input field, as reflected in the updated status of demo_element_1, where the text attribute now contained "Hj". The input field remained focused and visible, and the Submit button (demo_element_2) was unaffected by this action, still visible on the screen with its specified coordinates and text."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 58 [10-106], Y: 98 [83-114], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to activate the Submit button and complete the task of submitting the entered text "Hj" into the text field. The arguments for this action specify the type of the screen element as a button, with center coordinates X: 58 and Y: 98, and a horizontal range from 10 to 106 and a vertical range from 83 to 114. The text on the button was "Submit," indicating its function. This action was necessary because, after entering the text into the input field, the next step in the task was to submit that text, which is done by clicking the Submit button. The button was visible on the screen, making it possible to interact with it. After the action was performed, the status of the computer screen showed an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the previous screen elements were no longer displayed, likely due to the submission process leading to a new screen or the closing of the current window."}

