TASK:
Enter "Tula" into the text field and press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 80 [15-144], Y: 80 [69-91], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the text "Tula" needed to be entered. The arguments for this action were derived from the properties of demo_element_1, which is an input field located at the center of the screen with coordinates X: 80 and Y: 80, within the horizontal range of 15 to 144 and the vertical range of 69 to 91. This field was initially empty and visible, as indicated by the text attribute being an empty string and the visible attribute being True. The action was necessary to place the cursor inside the input field, making it ready for text entry. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused, as shown by the addition of the focused attribute set to True. This change meant that the input field was now active and ready to receive the text that the expert was about to type in the next action. The Submit button (demo_element_2) remained unchanged, still visible on the screen with its center coordinates slightly adjusted to X: 64 and Y: 116."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Tula", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `type_text` action, to enter the text "Tula" into the input field that was already focused from the previous action. The `type_text` action is necessary because it simulates typing on a keyboard, allowing the user to input text into an active text field. The argument "Tula" is the string of text that needed to be entered into the input field, as specified by the task. The input field, referred to as demo_element_1, was located at the center of the screen with coordinates X: 80 and Y: 80, within the horizontal range of 15 to 144 and the vertical range of 69 to 91. It was initially empty, as indicated by the text attribute being an empty string, and it was focused and visible, which meant it was ready to receive text. After the action was performed, the text "Tula" appeared within demo_element_1, as reflected by the updated text attribute in the status of the screen. The input field remained focused and visible, and the Submit button (demo_element_2) remained unchanged, indicating that the screen was ready for the next action to submit the entered data."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 64 [15-112], Y: 116 [99-132], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_4 was chosen by the expert to submit the text "Tula" that had been entered into the input field (demo_element_1). The action taken was a `click_element` action, which is used to activate or select a button or link on the screen. The arguments for this action were based on the properties of demo_element_2, which is a button with the label "Submit." This button was located on the screen with its center at X: 64 and Y: 116, within the horizontal range of 15 to 112 and the vertical range of 99 to 132. The button was visible, as indicated by the visible attribute being True. Clicking this button was necessary to complete the task of submitting the entered text, as per the task instructions. After the action was performed, the screen status showed an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application had likely processed the submission and moved on from the current screen, awaiting further user interaction or displaying a new screen as part of its workflow."}

