TASK:
Highlight the text in the paragraph below and click submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: drag_mouse_down, arg: {x=13, y=108}, element: {type: text, X: 63 [8-118], Y: 108 [103-114], text: "Molestie feugiat massa"}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `drag_mouse_hold_down` action, with the coordinates {x=13, y=108}, to initiate the process of highlighting the text in the paragraph. The coordinates correspond to the starting point of the text element "Molestie feugiat massa," which is visible on the screen with its center at X: 63 and Y: 108, and spans from the left edge at X: 8 to the right edge at X: 118, and from the top edge at Y: 103 to the bottom edge at Y: 114. This action was necessary to begin selecting the text by clicking and holding down the mouse button at the start of the text that needed to be highlighted. After this action, the status of the screen elements remained unchanged, as this action only marks the starting point for the drag operation to highlight the text and does not move any elements on the screen. The subsequent actions would involve dragging the mouse to select the text and then releasing the mouse button to complete the highlighting process."}
action_3: {name: drag_mouse_move, arg: {x=77, y=131}, displacement:{x_direction=64, y_direction=23}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `drag_mouse_move` action, with the arguments {x=77, y=131}. This action was chosen to continue the text highlighting process that began with action_2. The coordinates {x=77, y=131} were likely chosen because they represent a point diagonally across from the starting point of the drag, ensuring that all the text in the paragraph is covered by the drag action. The expert needed to move the mouse pointer while holding down the left mouse button to the end of the paragraph, which includes demo_element_2 ("Molestie feugiat massa"), demo_element_3 ("imperdiet. Mi massa pulvinar."), and demo_element_4 ("A. Ullamcorper"). After the action, the status of the screen showed that all three text elements were highlighted, indicating that the text was successfully selected. This is evident from the updated status of the elements, which now have the attribute `highlighted: True`, while the "Submit" button (demo_element_1) remained unchanged and visible."}
action_4: {name: drag_mouse_up, arg: {}, reason: "Action_4 was a `drag_mouse_release` action, which does not require any arguments because it simply involves releasing the left mouse button to complete the text highlighting process. The expert chose this action after having dragged the mouse pointer across the paragraph to highlight the text. This action was necessary to finalize the selection of the text, indicating to the computer that the highlighting task is complete. After the action was performed, the status of the screen elements remained unchanged from before the action, meaning that the text within demo_element_2 ("Molestie feugiat massa"), demo_element_3 ("imperdiet. Mi massa pulvinar."), and demo_element_4 ("A. Ullamcorper") stayed highlighted, and the "Submit" button (demo_element_1) remained visible and ready for the next action, which was to click it to submit the highlighted text."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 54 [6-102], Y: 72 [56-88], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_5 was a `click_element` action chosen by the expert to submit the highlighted text. The arguments for this action specified the target element as a button with the text "Submit," located at the center coordinates X: 54 and Y: 72, with its horizontal span from X: 6 to X: 102 and vertical span from Y: 56 to Y: 88. This button was visible on the screen, indicating that it was ready to be interacted with. The action was necessary because, after highlighting the text in the paragraph (as indicated by the `highlighted: True` status of demo_elements 2, 3, and 4), the next step in the task was to submit the selected text, which is achieved by clicking the "Submit" button. After the action was performed, the screen status showed an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application or window that contained the text and submit button was no longer displayed, likely due to the submission process closing it or navigating away from the current view."}

