TASK:
Search for mystery movies directed by Dotson from year 2012.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 100 [51-150], Y: 94 [83-105], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field for entering the genre of the movie. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates of the input field, which are X: 100 and Y: 94, indicating the center of the input field that is visible on the screen and labeled "Genre" (as indicated by demo_element_3). This input field (demo_element_2) was not focused before the action, meaning that any text typed would not have been entered into this field. The action was necessary to activate the input field so that the genre "mystery" could be typed into it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed from "focused: False" to "focused: True," indicating that the field was now active and ready to receive input. This is confirmed by the change in the status of demo_element_2, which now has the "focused" attribute set to True, showing that the field is selected and any subsequent text entered will appear in this field."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "mystery", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `type_text` action, to enter the genre "mystery" into the input field that was focused on the screen. The input field (demo_element_2) was previously focused by action_2, making it ready to receive text input. This input field is located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 94, and it is labeled "Genre" as indicated by the nearby text element (demo_element_3) with the text "Genre" at coordinates X: 32, Y: 93. The action was necessary to specify the genre of the movies the user wanted to search for, which in this case is "mystery." After the action was performed, the text "mystery" appeared in the input field (demo_element_2), confirming that the genre had been successfully entered. The input field remained focused, and the text "mystery" was visible within it, indicating that the system was ready to accept further search parameters or to proceed with the search."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 100 [51-149], Y: 119 [108-130], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the second input field for entering the year of the movie. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates of the input field, which are X: 100 and Y: 119, indicating the center of the input field that is visible on the screen and labeled "Year" (as indicated by demo_element_5). This input field (demo_element_4) was not focused before the action, meaning that any text typed would not have been entered into this field. The action was necessary to activate the input field so that the year "2012" could be typed into it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed from "focused: False" to "focused: True," indicating that the field was now active and ready to receive input. This is confirmed by the change in the status of demo_element_4, which now has the "focused" attribute set to True, showing that the field is selected and any subsequent text entered will appear in this field. The previously focused input field for the genre (demo_element_2) changed to "focused: False," indicating it was no longer the active field for text entry."}
action_5: {name: type_text, arg: "2012", reason: "The expert chose action_5, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "2012", to enter the year into the focused input field for the movie search. This action was necessary because the previous action (action_4) had focused on the input field specifically designated for entering the year of the movie, which is demo_element_4 located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 118. This input field is labeled "Year" as indicated by the nearby text element (demo_element_5) with the text "Year" at coordinates X: 36, Y: 118. By typing "2012" into this field, the expert specified the year for the movie search criteria. After the action was performed, the text "2012" appeared in the input field (demo_element_4), confirming that the year had been successfully entered. The input field remained focused, indicating that it was still active and could receive further input if necessary. The visibility of the input field and the text within it ensured that the user could see the entered search parameter for the year."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 100 [51-150], Y: 144 [132-155], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_6, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the third input field for entering the name of the director. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates of the input field, which are X: 100 and Y: 144, indicating the center of the input field that is visible on the screen and labeled "Director" (as indicated by demo_element_7). This input field (demo_element_6) was not focused before the action, meaning that any text typed would not have been entered into this field. The action was necessary to activate the input field so that the name "Dotson" could be typed into it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed from "focused: False" to "focused: True," indicating that the field was now active and ready to receive input. This is confirmed by the change in the status of demo_element_6, which now has the "focused" attribute set to True, showing that the field is selected and any subsequent text entered will appear in this field. The previously focused input field for the year (demo_element_4) changed to "focused: False," indicating it was no longer the active field for text entry."}
action_7: {name: type_text, arg: "Dotson", reason: "The expert chose action_7, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "Dotson", to enter the name of the director into the focused input field designated for the director's name. This action was necessary because the previous action (action_6) had focused on the input field specifically for entering the director's name, which is demo_element_6 located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 144. This input field is labeled "Director" as indicated by the nearby text element (demo_element_7) with the text "Director" at coordinates X: 28, Y: 144. By typing "Dotson" into this field, the expert specified the director's name for the movie search criteria. After the action was performed, the text "Dotson" appeared in the input field (demo_element_6), confirming that the director's name had been successfully entered. The input field remained focused, indicating that it was still active and could receive further input if necessary. The visibility of the input field and the text within it ensured that the user could see the entered search parameter for the director's name."}
action_8: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 80 [51-108], Y: 170 [161-180], text: "Submit", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_8, which is a `click_element` action, to submit the search query. The arguments for this action indicate that the expert clicked on a button with the text "Submit," located at the center coordinates X: 80 and Y: 170. This button (demo_element_8) was visible on the screen but not focused, meaning it was not the active element at that moment. Clicking the "Submit" button was necessary to execute the search with the specified parameters: the genre "mystery" (entered in demo_element_2), the year "2012" (entered in demo_element_4), and the director's name "Dotson" (entered in demo_element_6). After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an empty screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully. This implies that the search was executed, and the system likely moved to a different screen to display the search results or to process the query, which is why the previous screen elements were no longer visible."}

