TASK:
Search for satire movies directed by Townsend from year 1995.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 106 [62-149], Y: 72 [61-83], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the first input field on the screen, where the year of the movies needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the element ID to ensure the correct field is targeted. This action was necessary because before action_2, the input field for the year (demo_element_1) was not focused, as indicated by the `focused: False` status. This field is described as an input field located near the center-top of the screen with coordinates X: 106 [62-149], Y: 72 [61-83], and it was empty and visible. The label "Year:" (demo_element_2) next to it suggests that this is where the year should be entered. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed such that demo_element_1 became focused (`focused: True`), indicating that the input field was now active and ready to receive text input from the user. This change in focus is essential for the user to be able to type in the desired year for the movie search."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "1995", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "1995", to enter the year into the focused input field (demo_element_1) on the screen. This action was necessary because the task required searching for movies from the year 1995, and after action_2, the input field for the year was focused and ready to receive text input. The input field is described as being located near the center-top of the screen with coordinates X: 106 [62-149], Y: 72 [61-82], and it was empty and visible before the text was entered. After action_3 was performed, the status of the screen changed such that the text "1995" appeared in demo_element_1, indicating that the year was successfully entered into the input field. The field remained focused and visible, which is essential for the search criteria to be correctly set before proceeding with the search."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 106 [62-150], Y: 103 [92-114], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the second input field on the screen, where the director's name needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the element ID to ensure the correct field is targeted. This action was necessary because the task required searching for movies directed by Townsend, and after action_3, the input field for the director's name (demo_element_3) was not focused, as indicated by the `focused: False` status. This field is described as an input field located below the first input field (for the year) with coordinates X: 106 [62-150], Y: 103 [92-114], and it was empty and visible. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed such that demo_element_3 became focused (`focused: True`), indicating that the input field was now active and ready to receive text input from the user. The previously focused field for the year (demo_element_1) became unfocused (`focused: False`), which is a standard behavior when a new field is selected. This change in focus is essential for the user to be able to type in the director's name for the movie search."}
action_5: {name: type_text, arg: "Townsend", reason: "Action_5 was a `type_text` action with the argument "Townsend," chosen by the expert to enter the director's name into the second input field (demo_element_3) on the screen, which was focused and ready for text input. This action was necessary because the task specified searching for movies directed by Townsend, and after action_4, the input field for the director's name was the active field. This input field is described as being located below the first input field (for the year) and above the third input field (for the genre), with coordinates X: 106 [62-150], Y: 102 [92-113], and it was empty and visible before the text was entered. After action_5 was performed, the status of the screen changed such that the text "Townsend" appeared in demo_element_3, indicating that the director's name was successfully entered into the input field. The field remained focused and visible, which is essential for the search criteria to be correctly set before proceeding with the search."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 106 [62-150], Y: 134 [123-145], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_6, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the third input field on the screen, where the genre of the movies needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the element ID to ensure the correct field is targeted. This action was necessary because the task required searching for satire movies, and after action_5, the input field for the genre (demo_element_5) was not focused, as indicated by the `focused: False` status. This field is described as an input field located below the second input field (for the director's name) with coordinates X: 106 [62-150], Y: 134 [123-145], and it was empty and visible. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed such that demo_element_5 became focused (`focused: True`), indicating that the input field was now active and ready to receive text input from the user. The previously focused field for the director's name (demo_element_3) became unfocused (`focused: False`), which is a standard behavior when a new field is selected. This change in focus is essential for the user to be able to type in the genre for the movie search."}
action_7: {name: type_text, arg: "satire", reason: "Action_7 was a `type_text` action with the argument "satire," chosen by the expert to enter the genre into the third input field (demo_element_5) on the screen. This action was necessary because the task specified searching for satire movies, and after action_6, the input field for the genre was focused, as indicated by its `focused: True` status. This input field is described as being located below the second input field (for the director's name) with coordinates X: 106 [62-150], Y: 134 [123-144], and it was empty and visible before the text was entered. After action_7 was performed, the status of the screen changed such that the text "satire" appeared in demo_element_5, indicating that the genre was successfully entered into the input field. The field remained focused and visible, which is essential for the search criteria to be correctly set before proceeding with the search. The rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, with the year and director's name still present in their respective fields and the "Submit" button ready to be activated for the search."}
action_8: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 30 [2-59], Y: 165 [154-176], text: "Submit", focused: False}, reason: "The expert chose action_8, which is a `click_element` action, to activate the "Submit" button (demo_element_7) on the screen. This action was necessary to initiate the search based on the criteria entered into the input fields: the year "1995" in demo_element_1, the director's name "Townsend" in demo_element_3, and the genre "satire" in demo_element_5. The "Submit" button is described as a button located towards the bottom-left of the screen with coordinates X: 30 [2-59], Y: 165 [154-176], and the text "Submit" on it, indicating its function to submit the search query. It was not focused but was visible, which means it was ready to be clicked to perform the search. After action_8 was performed, the status of the computer screen changed to an empty screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the search results were presumably being processed or displayed on a different screen or window, which is a common behavior for search forms after submission."}

