TASK:
Search for satire movies directed by Townsend from year 1995.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 100 [51-150], Y: 94 [83-105], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the director's name needed to be entered. The input field for the director's name was identified as demo_element_2, located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 94, with the boundaries of the element stretching from 51 to 150 on the X-axis and from 83 to 105 on the Y-axis. This field was labeled with the text "Director" (demo_element_3) and was visible but not focused before the action. Clicking on this input field was necessary to place the cursor inside it, allowing for text entry in the subsequent step. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed such that demo_element_2 became focused, indicated by the `focused: True` status. This meant that the input field was now active, and the cursor was blinking inside it, ready for the expert to type in the director's name, "Townsend," which was done in the following action (action_3)."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Townsend", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "Townsend", to enter the name of the director into the focused input field. This action was necessary because, after action_2, demo_element_2—an input field located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 94, with the boundaries of the element stretching from 51 to 150 on the X-axis and from 83 to 104 on the Y-axis—was focused and ready for text entry. This field was associated with the label "Director" (demo_element_3), indicating that it was the correct place to type in the director's name for the search. After the `type_text` action was performed, the text "Townsend" appeared within demo_element_2, confirming that the director's name was successfully entered into the input field. The field remained focused, and the screen otherwise showed no significant changes, allowing the expert to proceed with the next steps of the task."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 100 [51-149], Y: 119 [108-130], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which was a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field for entering the year of the movie. This input field was identified as demo_element_4, located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 119, with the boundaries of the element stretching from 51 to 149 on the X-axis and from 108 to 130 on the Y-axis. The field was labeled with the text "Year" (demo_element_5) and was visible but not focused before the action. Clicking on this input field was necessary to place the cursor inside it, allowing for text entry of the year "1995" in the subsequent step (action_5). After action_4 was performed, the status of the screen changed such that demo_element_4 became focused, indicated by the `focused: True` status, while demo_element_2, previously focused, became unfocused. This meant that the input field for the year was now active, and the cursor was blinking inside it, ready for the expert to type in the year "1995". The rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, maintaining their visibility and focus status as before."}
action_5: {name: type_text, arg: "1995", reason: "The expert chose action_5, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "1995", to enter the year of the movie into the currently focused input field. This action was necessary because the previous action (action_4) had focused on demo_element_4, an input field for entering the year of the movie. This field is located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 118, with the boundaries stretching from 51 to 149 on the X-axis and from 108 to 129 on the Y-axis. It was labeled with the text "Year" (demo_element_5), indicating that it was the correct place to type in the year for the search. After the `type_text` action was performed, the text "1995" appeared within demo_element_4, confirming that the year was successfully entered. The field remained focused, which is indicated by the cursor still blinking within it, and the rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, maintaining their visibility and focus status as before."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 100 [51-149], Y: 144 [132-155], text: "", focused: False}, reason: "The expert performed action_6, which was a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field for entering the movie genre. This input field was identified as demo_element_6, located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 144, with the boundaries of the element stretching from 51 to 149 on the X-axis and from 132 to 155 on the Y-axis. The field was labeled with the text "Genre" (demo_element_7) and was visible but not focused before the action. Clicking on this input field was necessary to place the cursor inside it, allowing for text entry of the genre "satire" in the subsequent step (action_7). After action_6 was performed, the status of the screen changed such that demo_element_6 became focused, indicated by the `focused: True` status, while demo_element_4, previously focused, became unfocused. This meant that the input field for the genre was now active, and the cursor was blinking inside it, ready for the expert to type in the genre "satire". The rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, maintaining their visibility and focus status as before."}
action_7: {name: type_text, arg: "satire", reason: "The expert performed action_7, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "satire", to enter the genre of the movie into the currently focused input field. This action was necessary because the previous action (action_6) had focused on demo_element_6, an input field for entering the movie genre. This field is located at the center coordinates X: 100 and Y: 144, with the boundaries stretching from 51 to 150 on the X-axis and from 133 to 154 on the Y-axis. It was labeled with the text "Genre" (demo_element_7), indicating that it was the correct place to type in the genre for the search. After the `type_text` action was performed, the text "satire" appeared within demo_element_6, confirming that the genre was successfully entered. The field remained focused, which is indicated by the cursor still blinking within it, and the rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, maintaining their visibility and focus status as before."}
action_8: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 79 [50-108], Y: 170 [161-180], text: "Submit", focused: False}, reason: "The expert performed action_8, which was a `click_element` action, to submit the search query. The action targeted demo_element_8, which is a button element with the text "Submit" on it. This button was located at the center coordinates X: 79 and Y: 170, with the boundaries of the element stretching from 50 to 108 on the X-axis and from 161 to 180 on the Y-axis. Clicking the "Submit" button was necessary to execute the search with the criteria that had been entered into the input fields: the director's name "Townsend" in demo_element_2, the year "1995" in demo_element_4, and the genre "satire" in demo_element_6. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an empty screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully. This means that the search was executed, and the current search interface was no longer displayed, likely because the system was processing the search or had navigated to a results page."}

