TASK:
Enter the value that corresponds with each label into the form and submit when done.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 114 [70-157], Y: 144 [137-150], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field associated with the "Year of Birth" label. This action was necessary to activate the input field for text entry. The arguments for this action included the type of element (`input_field`) and its coordinates on the screen (X: 114 [70-157], Y: 144 [137-150]), which are the center and edge coordinates of the input field located next to the "Year of Birth:" label (demo_element_11). This label was visible on the screen with its own coordinates (X: 33 [4-62], Y: 142 [136-148]), indicating its position relative to the input field. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed to show that the input field (demo_element_12) was now focused, as indicated by the attribute `focused: True`. The coordinates of the input field slightly adjusted to X: 114 [69-158], Y: 143 [136-150], reflecting the precise location of the focused field. This focus state is essential for the next step, which is entering the "Year of Birth" value into the field."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "1949", reason: "The expert chose action_3, a `type_text` action, with the argument "1949" because the previous action (action_2) had successfully focused on the input field next to the "Year of Birth:" label (demo_element_11), which is an empty input field (demo_element_12) located at the center coordinates X: 114, Y: 143. The "Year of Birth" value needed to be entered into this field, and since the field was focused and ready for text entry, typing the text "1949" was the logical next step. This value corresponds to the "Year of Birth" information found in the tabled text (demo_element_6) at coordinates X: 118, Y: 94. After the action was completed, the status of the screen changed to show that the input field (demo_element_12) now contained the text "1949", indicating that the value had been successfully entered into the form. The field remained focused, allowing for further actions to be taken if necessary."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 114 [70-157], Y: 159 [152-166], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, a `click_element` action, to focus on the next input field for entering the "Language" value. The action's arguments specified the type of element (`input_field`) and its coordinates (X: 114 [70-157], Y: 159 [152-166]), which are the center and edge coordinates of the input field located next to the "Language:" label (demo_element_13). This label was visible on the screen with its own coordinates (X: 28 [5-52], Y: 157 [151-163]), indicating its position relative to the input field. Focusing on this input field was necessary because the previous field for "Year of Birth" (demo_element_12) had already been filled with the value "1949" and the task required entering the "Language" value into the form. After action_4 was performed, the status of the screen changed to show that the "Language" input field (demo_element_14) was now focused, as indicated by the attribute `focused: True`, and the coordinates slightly adjusted to X: 113 [69-157], Y: 158 [152-165], reflecting the precise location of the focused field. This change indicated that the input field was ready for text entry, which would be the next step in completing the form."}
action_5: {name: type_text, arg: "Javanese", reason: "The expert chose action_5, a `type_text` action, with the argument "Javanese" because the previous action (action_4) had successfully focused on the input field next to the "Language:" label (demo_element_13). This input field (demo_element_14) was empty and ready for text entry, located at the center coordinates X: 113 [69-157], Y: 158 [152-165]. The value "Javanese" was taken from the tabled text (demo_element_4) at coordinates X: 118 [80-155], Y: 78 [70-86], which corresponds to the "Language" label (demo_element_3). Entering this value into the focused input field was necessary to complete the form as per the task instructions. After the action was completed, the status of the screen changed to show that the input field (demo_element_14) now contained the text "Javanese", indicating that the value had been successfully entered. The field remained focused, with its coordinates slightly adjusted to X: 113 [69-157], Y: 159 [152-166], ready for any further actions if needed."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 52 [5-100], Y: 182 [167-198], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_6, a `click_element` action, to submit the completed form. The arguments for this action specified the type of element (`button`) and its coordinates (X: 52 [5-100], Y: 182 [167-198]), which are the center and edge coordinates of the "Submit" button (demo_element_15) located on the screen. This button was visible and labeled "Submit," indicating its function to finalize and send the form data. The action was necessary because the previous input fields for "Year of Birth" (demo_element_12) and "Language" (demo_element_14) had been filled with their respective values, "1949" and "Javanese," and the form was ready to be submitted. After the action was performed, the status of the computer screen showed an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the form had been submitted, as there were no more elements displayed on the screen."}

