TASK:
Enter the value of Last name into the text field and press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 70 [6-135], Y: 144 [133-154], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the last name needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the type of the element to interact with. In this case, the input field (demo_element_11) is located at the center coordinates X: 70 and Y: 144, with the left and right edges spanning from 6 to 135 on the X-axis and the top and bottom edges from 133 to 154 on the Y-axis. This action was necessary to activate the input field so that text could be entered into it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused (as shown by the attribute `focused: True`), which means that the cursor was placed inside the input field, ready for text entry. The slight change in the coordinates of the input field to X: 71 and Y: 142 is a normal screen update that reflects the element's active state."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Carter", reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `type_text` action, to enter the last name "Carter" into the focused input field. This action was necessary because the task required entering the value of the last name into the text field before submitting it. The input field (demo_element_11) was already focused from the previous action, as indicated by its status showing `focused: True`. The argument "Carter" for the `type_text` action was chosen because it is the text associated with the "Last name" label (demo_element_7) on the screen, which was visible and located at X: 126 [97-154], Y: 106 [99-114]. After the action was completed, the status of the input field (demo_element_11) updated to show the text "Carter" within it, confirming that the last name was successfully entered, ready for the next step of the task, which would be to submit the entered information."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 54 [7-102], Y: 169 [153-185], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to interact with the "Submit" button on the screen. The arguments for this action specify the type of the element as a button, with center coordinates at X: 54 and Y: 169, and the text "Submit" on it. The button's horizontal span is from 7 to 102 on the X-axis, and its vertical span is from 153 to 185 on the Y-axis. This action was necessary to submit the entered last name "Carter" in the input field (demo_element_11), which was the task's requirement. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application likely processed the submission and moved to a different state or screen as part of its normal operation."}

