TASK:
Scroll the textarea to the top of the text hit submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: drag_mouse_down, arg: {x=148, y=103}, element: {type: scrollbar_thumb, X: 148 [138-157], Y: 104 [96-112]}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `drag_mouse_hold_down` action, with the coordinates {x=148, y=103}, to initiate the scrolling of the text area to the top. The coordinates correspond to the scrollbar's thumb element (demo_element_7), which is a draggable control within a vertical scrollbar that allows users to adjust the view of the content within the text area (demo_element_1). The thumb element was located at the center X coordinate of 148 and center Y coordinate of 104, within the bounds of 138-157 for X and 96-112 for Y. The action was necessary because the task required scrolling the text area to the top before hitting the submit button, and dragging the scrollbar's thumb is the way to manually scroll the content.

After the action_2, the screen status showed that the text area remained focused and visible, indicating that the scrollbar's thumb was successfully engaged for scrolling, but the actual scrolling effect would be observed in subsequent actions (action_3) where the thumb is moved to a new position, resulting in the text area content being scrolled. The coordinates of some text elements (demo_element_2 and demo_element_10) slightly changed, which could be due to the scrollbar interaction, but the main scrolling effect would be seen after the thumb is moved."}
action_3: {name: drag_mouse_move, arg: {x=147, y=78}, displacement:{x_direction=-1, y_direction=-25}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `drag_mouse_move` action, with the arguments {x=147, y=78}, to scroll the text area to the top. This action was necessary because the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_7), initially located at X: 148 [138-157], Y: 104 [96-112], needed to be moved upwards to scroll the text area (demo_element_1) content upwards. By moving the thumb towards the up button (demo_element_3) of the scrollbar, located at X: 148 [138-157], Y: 66 [57-76], the text area content would move in the opposite direction, revealing the text at the top. After the action, the thumb's new position was at X: 148 [138-157], Y: 84 [76-91], indicating a successful scroll upwards. As a result, the previously visible text elements (demo_element_2, demo_element_4 to demo_element_13) became invisible, and new text elements (demo_element_16 to demo_element_24) appeared at the top of the text area, showing that the content had indeed been scrolled up, revealing the beginning of the text."}
action_4: {name: drag_mouse_up, arg: {}, reason: "Action_4, which is a `drag_mouse_release` action, was chosen by the expert to complete the scrolling process initiated by the previous drag actions. This action is necessary to release the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_3) after dragging it to the desired position, which in this case was to scroll the text area (demo_element_1) to the top. The `drag_mouse_release` action does not require specific arguments as it simply signals the end of the dragging motion. After this action was performed, the status of the screen components remained unchanged from the status before the action, indicating that the thumb remained at the new position (X: 148 [138-157], Y: 84 [76-91]), and the text area remained scrolled to the top with the new text elements (demo_element_16 to demo_element_24) visible at the top of the text area, confirming that the scrolling action was successful and complete."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [2-98], Y: 180 [164-196], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_5, which is a `click_element` action, to submit the form after scrolling the textarea to the top. The action was necessary to complete the task as instructed. The `click_element` action was performed on demo_element_15, which is a button with the text "Submit" located at the center X coordinate of 50 (within the bounds of 2-98) and center Y coordinate of 180 (within the bounds of 164-196). This button was visible and needed to be activated to submit the contents of the text area (demo_element_1), which had been scrolled to the top as required. After the action was performed, the screen status showed an empty screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the form was likely submitted, resulting in the user being taken to a different screen or the application performing an action that cleared the current screen."}

