TASK:
Find the last word in the text area, enter it into the text field and hit Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 65 [1-129], Y: 170 [159-180], text: ""}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a `click_element` action on the input field (demo_element_10), to place the cursor inside the input field so that text could be entered. The input field was located at the center coordinates X: 65, Y: 170, with its edges spanning from X: 1 to 129 and Y: 159 to 180, and it was initially empty and visible on the screen. This action was necessary because, in order to complete the task of entering the last word from the text area into the input field, the input field must first be active and ready to receive text input. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused (as shown by the attribute `focused: True`), which means that the cursor was blinking inside the input field, and any subsequent text typed would appear there. The rest of the screen components remained unchanged, with all text and elements still visible."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Risus", reason: "The expert performed action_3, which was a `type_text` action with the argument "Risus", to enter the last word found in the text area into the focused input field (demo_element_10). This action was necessary because the task required finding the last word in the text area and entering it into the text field. The last word "Risus" was identified from the text within demo_element_8, which read "purus, volutpat. Risus.", and was visible on the screen with its center coordinates at X: 60, Y: 128. After the `type_text` action was executed, the status of the input field (demo_element_10) changed to contain the text "Risus", indicating that the word had been successfully entered. The input field was still focused, ready for further actions, and the rest of the screen components remained unchanged."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 196 [183-210], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which was a `click_element` action on the "Submit" button (demo_element_11), to submit the text that was entered into the input field. The "Submit" button was identified by its type, coordinates, and text label. It was located at the center coordinates X: 50, Y: 196, with its edges spanning from X: 1 to 98 and Y: 183 to 210, and it was labeled with the text "Submit". This action was necessary to complete the task, as the last word "Risus" had already been entered into the input field (demo_element_10), and the next step was to submit this input for processing. After the action was executed, the screen status showed an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application likely transitioned to a different state or screen as a result of the submission, which is why no elements were visible anymore."}

