TASK:
Solve the math problem and type your answer into the textbox. Press submit when done.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 126 [102-150], Y: 80 [61-98], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to activate the input field where the answer to the math problem needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the element to interact with, in this case, demo_element_1, which is an input field located at the center coordinates X: 126 and Y: 80 on the screen. This input field was initially empty and visible, as indicated by the text attribute being an empty string and the visible attribute being True. The action was necessary to focus on the input field so that text could be entered into it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused, as shown by the addition of the attribute `focused: True`. This focus allows for subsequent text entry, which is required to solve the task of entering the answer to the math problem "4 - 5 =". The location and visibility of the input field remained the same, ensuring that the expert could proceed with typing the answer into the now-active field."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "-1", reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `type_text` action, with the argument "-1" to enter the solution to the math problem displayed on the screen. The math problem "4 - 5 =" was presented in demo_element_2, a text element located at the center coordinates X: 51 and Y: 76, and the solution to this simple subtraction problem is -1. Since demo_element_1, an input field located at the center coordinates X: 126 and Y: 79, was already focused (as indicated by the `focused: True` attribute), it was ready to receive text input. Typing the answer into this field was necessary to complete the task of solving the math problem. After the action was executed, the status of the input field (demo_element_1) changed to include the text "-1", indicating that the answer was successfully entered. The input field remained focused and visible, and the other elements on the screen, including the math problem and the "Submit" button (demo_element_3), remained unchanged."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 80 [31-128], Y: 132 [116-149], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to interact with demo_element_3, a button element labeled "Submit" located at the center coordinates X: 80 and Y: 132 on the screen. This action was necessary to submit the answer "-1" that was previously entered into the input field (demo_element_1). The "Submit" button was visible and needed to be activated to complete the task of solving the math problem. By clicking on this button, the expert signaled the system to process the entered answer. After the action was executed, the screen status changed to an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the interface for the math problem was no longer displayed, which typically means that the submission was accepted and the task was concluded."}

