TASK:
Solve for x and type your answer into the textbox. Press Submit when done.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 106 [76-136], Y: 109 [90-128], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the solution for "x" needs to be entered. The input field is described as having its center at coordinates X: 106, Y: 109, with a horizontal range from 76 to 136 and a vertical range from 90 to 128. It was empty ("text: """) and visible on the screen. Focusing on this input field is necessary because it allows the user to type in the answer. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused ("focused: True"), which means that the cursor was now active in the input field, ready for the user to type in the solution. The rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, with their positions and visibility consistent with their state before the action."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "58", reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "58", to enter the solution for the equation "x - 4 = 54" into the input field. This equation was displayed on the screen as part of demo_element_1, with the text "x - 4 = 54" visible at coordinates X: 78, Y: 67. The input field, identified as demo_element_2, was already focused (ready for text entry) and located at coordinates X: 106, Y: 110. The expert deduced the solution to the equation by adding 4 to 54, resulting in 58, which is the value for "x". This action was necessary to solve the given task, which was to find the value of "x" and type it into the input field. After the action was completed, the text "58" appeared in the input field (demo_element_2), indicating that the answer was successfully entered. The input field remained focused, and the rest of the screen elements stayed unchanged, with their visibility and text content as before."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 79 [30-128], Y: 162 [146-179], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to interact with the "Submit" button, identified as demo_element_4. This button was described as having its center at coordinates X: 79, Y: 162, with a horizontal range from 30 to 128 and a vertical range from 146 to 179, and the text "Submit" was visible on it. Clicking this button was necessary to submit the answer "58" that was entered into the input field (demo_element_2) for the equation "x - 4 = 54" (demo_element_1). The "Submit" button is a common user interface element that, when activated, typically triggers the processing of entered data. After the expert performed action_4, the screen status changed to an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application had likely moved on from the current task screen, either to a confirmation message, the next task, or it had closed the task window."}

