TASK:
Select -1 with the spinner and hit Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: scrollbar_down_button, X: 144 [136-153], Y: 82 [76-87]}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a click on the down button of a spinner, to decrease the value in the associated input field. The down button of the spinner is identified as demo_element_4, located at the center coordinates X: 144 and Y: 82, with the visible range of X coordinates from 136 to 153 and Y coordinates from 76 to 87. This action was necessary because the task required selecting the value "-1" in the input field, and since the initial value was "0" as shown by demo_element_2, clicking the down button would decrement the value by one. After the action was performed, the status of the screen changed as follows: the text in the input field (demo_element_2) was updated to "-1", indicating that the value had been successfully decreased by one, and the input field was now focused, ready for further interaction or submission. The rest of the elements on the screen remained visible and unchanged."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 53 [5-101], Y: 106 [91-122], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which was a click on the "Submit" button, to finalize the selection of the value "-1" in the input field and complete the task. The "Submit" button is identified as demo_element_5, located at the center coordinates X: 53 and Y: 106, with the visible range of X coordinates from 5 to 101 and Y coordinates from 91 to 122. The button was clearly labeled with the text "Submit," indicating its function to submit the form or data entered. This action was necessary because, after selecting the desired value "-1" in the input field (demo_element_2) using the down button of the spinner (demo_element_4), the next step was to submit that value to complete the task. After the expert clicked the "Submit" button, the task was completed successfully, resulting in an empty screen, which signifies that the user interface for the task was no longer displayed, indicating the end of the task."}

