TASK:
Enter an item that starts with "Sao " and ends with "pe".

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 74 [9-138], Y: 81 [70-92], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to activate the input field where the item text needs to be entered. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the type of the screen element to interact with. In this case, the input field (demo_element_2) is located at the center coordinates X: 74 and Y: 81, with the horizontal range from 9 to 138 and the vertical range from 70 to 92. This input field was empty and visible, indicating it was ready to receive input. The action was necessary because, in order to type text into an input field, the field must first be focused, which is achieved by clicking on it. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused (as shown by the addition of the `focused: True` attribute), meaning that it was now ready to accept the text input from the user."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Sao", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `type_text` action, to enter the beginning part of the desired item text into the already focused input field (demo_element_2). The input field was located at the center coordinates X: 74 and Y: 81, with a horizontal range from 9 to 138 and a vertical range from 70 to 92. The field was empty and focused, as indicated by the `text: ""` and `focused: True` attributes, respectively. Typing "Sao" was necessary because the task required entering an item that starts with "Sao ". After the action was performed, the text "Sac" appeared in the input field, which seems to be a typo since the expected text was "Sao". Additionally, the "Submit" button (demo_element_3) became invisible, and two new tabled_text elements appeared: demo_element_4 with the text "Principe" and demo_element_5 with the text "Sao Tome and", both of which were likely suggestions or auto-completions related to the text entered in the input field."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 74 [11-138], Y: 121 [112-130], text: "Principe"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, a `click_element` action, to select the suggested text "Principe" from the list of auto-completions that appeared after typing "Sac" into the input field. The arguments for this action specify that the element to be clicked is of type `tabled_text`, located at the center coordinates X: 74 and Y: 121, with a horizontal range from 11 to 138 and a vertical range from 112 to 130. This action was necessary because the task required entering an item that ends with "pe", and "Principe" fits this criterion while also correcting the initial typo "Sac" to "Sao". After the action was performed, the text in the input field (demo_element_2) was updated to "Sao Tome and Princ", the "Submit" button (demo_element_3) became visible again, indicating it could be clicked to submit the entry, and the auto-completion suggestions (demo_element_4 and demo_element_5) disappeared, as they were no longer needed."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 58 [9-106], Y: 112 [95-128], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_5 was a `click_element` action performed on demo_element_3, which is a button with the label "Submit". The button was located at the center coordinates X: 58 and Y: 112, with a horizontal range from 9 to 106 and a vertical range from 95 to 128. This action was necessary because, after correcting the initial typo and completing the input with "Sao Tome and Princ", the user needed to submit the entered data to complete the task. The "Submit" button was visible and clickable, indicating that it was the appropriate UI element to finalize the input process. After the action was executed, the screen became empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application had likely moved on from the current input screen, possibly to process the submitted data or to present a new task or screen to the user."}

